hey that's our show one quick thing
before we go uh I mentioned to you that
I would keep you up to date on any new
information we had about uh the
transition of the program all those
other things uh we do have some specific
information my last Daily Show program
uh will be August the 6th I will be
wearing a suit I will more than likely
be
showered I'm sorry I'll be wearing
overalls and I won't
shower kind of strange so uh I hope that
you will that you will join us for that
program uh and as a matter of fact you
can actually join us here in reality uh
enter a chance to win tickets to my
final episode of The Daily Show it's
going to be a pretty good episode I
think it' be flown to New York put up a
nice hotel uh you might even sit here
maybe I'll give you a little uh what do
you call it there selfies there and uh
all of the money goes to night of to
many stars New York collaborates for
autism go to omaze.com daow and then
maybe I'll see you here August 6 and
we'll have a nice hug we
hug